<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mj0stjo.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mj0stjo.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-06-11T15:24:17+00:00</updated><id>https://mj0stjo.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Johannes - mj0stjo</title><subtitle>Just a website about me and the stuff I do.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Work Experience Placement Throwback</title><link href="https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/throwback/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Work Experience Placement Throwback" /><published>2023-06-11T16:53:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-11T16:53:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/throwback</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/throwback/"><![CDATA[<p>As a dual student at Nokia, I am fortunate to participate in work experience placements during each semester break. Today, I want to share some impressions from my previous work experience placement in February with all of you. Please keep in mind that this post is from March, so don’t let the tenses confuse you! 😉</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Today, my third work experience placement at Nokia Technology Center in Ulm came to an end.</p>

  <p>The last four weeks, my colleagues and fellow students and I have continued our log file analysis project. Based on our findings from the last practical phase, we adapted an open-source command line tool to be able to process the log format we needed. This task required a deep understanding of the log structure, which we had fortunately already acquired last summer when we used various machine learning techniques to find anomalies in said log files. Additionally, we also gained further experience in working with Linux and the command line.</p>

  <p>It was very nice to see again how diverse work at Nokia is. In my last work experience placements, I have already worked with hardware, dived deep into research and now had the chance to work on an open-source project.
Now I’m looking forward to the next semester at Technische Hochschule Ulm, before I’ll be back at Nokia in summer, where I will have the chance to do my work experience placement abroad!</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="work" /><category term="Nokia" /><category term="LogAnalysis" /><category term="DualStudies" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throwback to my Work Experience Placement at Nokia in Feburary]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome…</title><link href="https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/welcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome…" /><published>2023-06-07T18:12:16+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-07T18:12:16+00:00</updated><id>https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mj0stjo.github.io/blog/2023/welcome/"><![CDATA[<p>👋 Hey there!</p>

<p>Welcome to my GitHub page! I’m a passionate computer science student and this is where I’ll be showcasing my ideas and projects. Through my blog, I’ll be sharing insights, tips, and my journey as I explore the vast world of computer science.</p>

<p>From coding challenges to innovative projects, I’ll be diving deep into various topics and technologies. Expect to see code snippets, tutorials, and my personal experiences along the way. Join me on this exciting adventure as we unravel the wonders of the digital realm.</p>

<p>Feel free to explore and connect. I’m thrilled to have you on this journey with me!</p>

<p>Happy coding! 💻🚀</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[...to my blog!]]></summary></entry></feed>